In the side position, we're going to be palming and thumbing the sen lines on the legs.
Now make sure your client is comfortable in the side position, supporting your head, knee supported, arms are resting in front comfortably.
So starting with palming on sen lines with this leg.
On the front leg you're going to be doing the outside.
And on the inside leg closest to you, you're going to be doing the inside.
So we're going to start with the inside leg first.
Placing the palm, placing the palm and then start in a nice rocking fashion.
Walking it up, rocking it down.
And you can do this as long or as short as the massage requires, time wise or your client's needs.
Coming to the other one, and again, just in a nice rocking position.
I lift it up enough to make sure that I'm comfortable.
Come back and forth.
Always make sure you get a little thumbing in there too.
So we're going to start again on this one.
Place the thumb, place the thumb, just on the side of leg, and just kind of, you'll feel that you'll feel a little groove in there so you're not pressing up on any bones.
And just thumb up and pressing in the thumb in the area where, my fingerprint would be not on the tips of that stabbing her with my fingernails.
Be very mindful of that.
Coming in here and again, nice rocking back and forth, back and forth.
Not applying too much thumb pressure, to not only save your own thumbs but to not kind of over press on your client.
Back and forth.
Always giving a little bit of Meta, a little loving kindness as you finish.